<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="infoArr">
        <item>The series follows "The Gang", a group of five depraved underachievers: twins Dennis Reynolds (Glenn Howerton) and Deandra "Sweet Dee" Reynolds (Kaitlin Olson), their friends Charlie Kelly (Charlie Day) and Ronald "Mac" McDonald (Rob McElhenney), and (from season 2 onward) Frank Reynolds (Danny DeVito), Dennis' and Dee's legal father. The Gang runs the dilapidated Paddy's Pub, an Irish bar in South Philadelphia.</item>
        <item>Bob\'s Burgers centers on the Belcher family (consists of Bob, Linda, Tina, Gene and Louise) who own a hamburger restaurant. ... Together, they run Bob\'s Burgers where the food is great but life always gets in the way of business.</item>
        <item>The show revolves around the adventures of the members of the Smith household, which consists of parents Jerry and Beth, their kids Summer and Morty, and Beth\'s father, Rick Sanchez, who lives with them as a guest.</item>
        <item>Parks and Recreation is an American political comedy television sitcom starring Amy Poehler as Leslie Knope, a perky, mid-level bureaucrat in the Parks Department of Pawnee, a fictional town in Indiana. Created by Greg Daniels and Michael Schur, the series aired on NBC from April 9, 2009 to February 24, 2015, for 125 episodes, over seven seasons.</item>
        <item>This U.S. adaptation -- set at a paper company based in Scranton, Pa. -- has a similar documentary style to that of the Ricky Gervais-led British original. It features the Dunder-Mifflin staff, which includes characters based on roles in the British show -- and, quite possibly, people with whom you work in your office.</item>
        <item>Community is an American television sitcom created by Dan Harmon that aired on NBC and Yahoo! Screen from September 17, 2009 to June 2, 2015. The series follows an ensemble cast of characters played by Joel McHale, Gillian Jacobs, Danny Pudi, Yvette Nicole Brown, Alison Brie, Donald Glover, Ken Jeong, Chevy Chase, and Jim Rash at a community college in the fictional town of Greendale, Colorado.</item>
        <item>Archer is an American adult animated spy sitcom created by Adam Reed for the FX network. The series focuses on the life and exploits of Sterling Archer, the self-proclaimed "world's greatest secret agent."</item>
        <item>Oscar-nominated actor William H. Macy stars as Frank Gallagher, a single father of six who spends much of his free time drinking at bars. The Gallagher children -- led by oldest daughter Fiona (Emmy Rossum), who takes on much of the child-rearing responsibility due to her mother\'s absence -- manage to raise themselves in spite of Frank's lack of parenting and unusual parenting style when he does choose to act like a father.</item>
        <item>Ted has fallen in love. It all started when his best friend, Marshall, drops the bombshell that he plans to propose to longtime girlfriend Lily, a kindergarten teacher. Suddenly, Ted realizes that he had better get a move on if he hopes to find true love. </item>
        <item>Michael Bluth finds himself forced to stay in Orange County and run the family real estate business after his father, George Bluth Sr., is sent to prison for committing white-collar crime.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
